Today, I am giving the Honnouji Academy Student Council system a fresh start!
（皐月(さつき)）本日！
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園生徒会の体制を
白紙に戻す
全ての生徒は全ての生徒への
攻撃権を持つ
All students are hereby granted
the right to attack all other students!
Secret meetings, scheming,
backstabbing—anything goes!
密議 陰謀 闇討ち 何でもありだ
Seven days from now,
reach the schoolyard alive!
７日後 生きて校庭にたどりつけ
First
Honnouji
Academy
Naturals
Election
And then, use your own strength to lay claim to your social standing once again!
そして己の地位を
己の力でつかみ直せ
This shall be Honnouji Academy's
first naturals election!
（皐月）これぞ…
FIRST
HONNOUJI
ACADEMY
NATURALS
ELECTION
"Naturals election"?
（流子(りゅうこ)）壊惨総戦挙(かいさんそうせんきょ)？
In this election, you will not
be choosing some candidate!
（皐月）戦挙とは お前たちが
誰かを選ぶのではない
You will be choosing yourself!
お前たち自身が
お前たち自身で選ぶのだ
Your standing! Your strength!
Your way of life!
その地位を 力を 生き方を！
At 8:30am, seven days from now,
７日後の午前８時30分
a sudden death runoff election will be held
with the survivors who arrive in this schoolyard!
この校庭にたどりついた者たちで
決戦闘兵(とうひょう)を行う
SUDDEN DEATH
RUNOFF
ELECTION
Fight one another! Emerge victorious!
互いに戦い 勝ち抜け
And I will grant you your
Ultima Uniforms anew!
改めて新しい極(ごく)制服を与えよう
Now, fellow comrades
...of Honnouji Academy...
さあ 本能字学園の同胞(はらから)よ
Fight!
戦え！
EPISODE 8
I WILL WIPE MY OWN TEARS
This is a world tailored to someone's whims and fancies
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
RYUUKO
MATOI
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
Or trip and fall
korondatte
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
Iori, begin.
（皐月）伊織(いおり) 始めろ
（伊織）はっ
Yes, milady.
Beginning High Velocity
Life Fiber Jammer Emission.
（伊織）生命戦維(せんい)超高速邪魔浴(じゃまー)
噴出開始
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）
細かく寸断した
生命戦維を—
The emitters circulate finely chopped Life Fibers at a speed of 100 m/s.
秒速１００メートルの
スピードで—
HIGH VELOCITY LIFE FIBER JAMMER
巡回させている
Any and all attacks are
neutralized by that barrier.
（美木杉）
あの糸のバリアーの前では
全ての攻撃は無効化される
鮮血(せんけつ)の力でも
突破は難しいだろうね
Even with Senketsu's power,
it would be very difficult to breach.
直接対決のいい機会だと
思ってたのに—
Damn. And here I thought this was
my chance to challenge her directly.
She whips everybody into a frenzy and
then sits behind an impenetrable shield?
あおるだけあおっといて
自分は鉄壁の防御の中かよ
It's probably the other way around.
たぶん逆だな 絶対支配していた
自分の存在を隠して—
She has ruled absolutely here, so by sequestering herself,
学園に無秩序状態を
もたらしてるんだ ほら
she causes a state of anarchy
within the academy. See?
I'm so sick of her crap.
まったく つきあいきれねえよ
（一つ星生徒）ダアー！
This is crazy.
（猿投山(さなげやま)）まいったな
Is she trying to tear down
the order she herself created?
一度 自分が作り上げた秩序を
自分の手で打ち壊すつもりかい
As always, she's taking
things to extremes.
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）相変わらず
やることが極端だね
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）それが鬼龍院(きりゅういん)皐月よ
やるとなったら容赦はない
That's Kiryuuin Satsuki in a nutshell.
If something needs to be done,
she doesn't hold back.
Still, this gives us a chance to let out some stress and enjoy ourselves.
でもまあ おかげで久しぶりに
羽が伸ばせるわ
Ah, I follow you. Personal time.
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）なるほど
自分のための時間か
では諸君 ７日後に
In that case, gentlemen,
I will see you in seven days.
...That sound just now...
Was that a car key?
（猿投山）
今の音 車のキーか？
（蛇崩）
最近 車の免許
取ったらしいの
I hear he got his license recently.
皐月様の送迎も
自分でやるつもりみたい
It sounds like he intends to serve as Lady Satsuki's chauffeur himself.
His dedication is admirable.
（犬牟田）
大した忠誠心だな
Okay, I guess we'll meet up
in seven days, too.
じゃ
あたしたちも７日後に
I don't think any of us are dumb enough not to make it to the Sudden Death Runoff Election.
まさか この中に
決戦闘兵に来れない—
まぬけは
いないと思うけど
（一つ星生徒）タアー
（一つ星生徒たち）カアー
The loincloth is mine!
（一つ星生徒）取ったー
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
Gosh, things sure are
crazy in town, huh?
（マコ）いやあ
町はひどい騒ぎだねぇ
（又郎(またろう)）
アチアチ アチャチャ
What's with you guys
looking all philosophical?
（流子）何だ みんな
妙に達観した顔で
Well, if there's one thing
that recent incident taught us,
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）目先の欲で
あくせくしてもしかたないのは—
it's that obsessing over
short-term wants isn't any good.
こないだの件で
よーくわかったからな
（又郎）そうそう
残りものには福がある
You said it.
There's luck in the last helping.
If I wait until everyone's exhausted from fighting, I'll be able to lift one or two wallets easy!
みんなが疲れ切ったところを
狙えば—
財布の１つや２つ
簡単にパクれらあ
（好代(すくよ)）又郎 懲りてない
（又郎）あっ 痛(いて)っ
Matarou, you never learn!
（薔薇蔵）ナハハッ
（又郎）痛てて 痛っ 痛てて…
In that case, sir,
I'm gonna borrow your scooter.
じゃあ おじさん
バイク借ります
（薔薇蔵）
流子ちゃんのために—
I swindled it from that scooter shop owner especially for you.
バイク屋のオヤジから
巻き上げたんだ
好きに使え
Use it all you like.
（マコ）流子ちゃん どこ行くの？
（流子）ちょっとね
Where are you going, Ryuuko?
Nowhere special.
（マコ）あっ ツーリングだね
（流子）おっ
Oh, just going for a ride, huh?
I'll go with you!
私もついていくよ
よーし レッツゴー！
Okay, let's go!
（鮮血(せんけつ)）ああっ！
（流子）お… おい
（マコ）離さないもん
Hey!
I'm not letting go!
Oh, what the hell.
まあ しかたないか
鮮血 ちょっと我慢してろ
Senketsu, just deal with it
for a little while.
...C-Can't breathe...
（鮮血）く… 苦しい
戦挙はいいのか？
Aren't you gonna fight in the election?
Nah, I'm a No-Star.
I don't have anything to lose.
どうせ無星だもん
失うものはないもん
むしろ１週間 学校休みで
ラッキーって感じよ
In fact, I'm happy 'cause
it's like a one-week vacation!
You have a point.
確かにな
We'll be outside cheering you on
in the Sudden Death Runoff Election,
あたしたちは決戦闘兵は
外野で応援してるから—
so fight hard, okay?
頑張ってね
Will do!
（流子）わかった
Matoi
Isshin
Ryuuko
...Is this...
（マコ）ここは…
（流子）あたしのウチだ
It's my family's house.
（マコ）こんな所が？
Whoa, this dump?
Wow, so you were poor, too!
流子ちゃんも貧乏してたんだね
焼け跡に住んでたんじゃないぞ
We didn't live in these
burnt-out ruins.
普通の屋敷だったけど
火事で焼け落ちたんだ
It was a regular mansion
back then, but it burned down.
Oh, it was?
なーんだ… って
じゃあ流子ちゃん お嬢様？
Wait, does that mean
you're a rich girl?!
（流子）そんなんじゃない
No, of course not.
My mom died right after I was born,
母さんは
私を産んですぐ死んで—
and my dad was a scientist
who only had time for his research.
父さんは
研究ばっかりの科学者で—
We never got along, so I started
living in the dorms in grade school.
仲も あまりうまくいってなくて
小学校から寮暮らしだった
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
Ox
Elementary
School
I broke bad and got into lots of fights.
（流子）私はグレて ケンカ三昧
By my first year of high school,
I was a full-blown juvenile delinquent.
高１のときには いっぱしの
ワルの出来上がりだ
And then, six months ago,
それが半年前
I got a message from Dad
saying that he wanted to talk,
父さんから“話がある”と
連絡があり—
久しぶりに帰ってきた が…
so I went home for
the first time in ages.
...But...
Dad! Dad!
（流子）
父さん！ 父さん 父さん
Dad!
（一身）騒ぐな流子
Don't make a scene, Ryuuko.
お前が平穏な人生を送りたければ
黙って去れ
If you want to live a peaceful life, just stand up and walk away.
But if you want to
...fight in my place...
俺の代わりに戦ってくれるなら…
（流子）ハッ
（一身）このハサミを持て
Take this scissor!
What do you mean, fight?
どういうことだ？
（一身）このハサミを持てば
必ず俺を殺した相手にたどりつく
If you take that scissor, you're sure to find the person who killed me.
だが お前には過酷な運命が待つ
But a cruel fate will lie in store for you.
Hold it!
（流子）待て！
（一身）追うな 流子
Let them go, Ryuuko!
There's still much
that I have to tell you!
お前に伝えなければならないことが
もっとある
...Dad...
（流子）父さん…
Dad!
父さーん！
When we lived apart,
there were times when I hated him.
（流子）離れて暮らしてるときは
恨んだこともあった
But when he died, I realized for the first time that I didn't know anything about my father.
でも 死んで初めて気が付いた
あたしは父さんのこと
何も知らないってね
So I wanted to at least
find out who killed him and why.
だから せめて誰が何のために
父さんを殺したのか
And what he was trying to tell me.
父さんが
何を言おうとしていたのか
このハサミは何なのか
And what this scissor really is.
それを突き止めたいと思ってるんだ
I want to find those answers.
And I want to know why
my dad created you, Senketsu.
鮮血 なぜ父さんが
お前を作ったのかもな
There's nothing here.
（流子）何もない
I thought that there might be some kind of clue
where I found you, but I guess it was a waste of time.
（流子）
お前を見つけた場所に—
何か手がかりが残ってないかと
思ったんだけど—
無駄足だったな
Mikisugi's doing, no doubt.
（鮮血）おそらく
美木杉の仕業だろう
Maybe.
かもな…
Sorry. Looks like Dad brought home a messed-up scooter.
（マコ）ごめんね 父ちゃんが
いいかげんなバイク持ってきて
I can't believe the
gas gauge was busted.
（流子）
まさか ガソリンメーターが
壊れてたとはな
Say, Ryuuko.
（マコ）ねえ 流子ちゃん
（流子）ん？
You have us now. You're not alone.
今は私たちがいるよ
流子ちゃん 独りじゃないよ
鮮血ちゃんだけじゃない
私も 私の家族も—
It's not just Senketsu.
My family and I love you,
Ryuuko. All of us.
みんな流子ちゃんのこと
大好きだよ
Sure, I know that.
ああ よくわかってるよ
Then let's hitchhike!
（マコ）
じゃあ ヒッチハイクで
（流子）何が？
（マコ）ヘイ ヘイヘイ！
Say what?
Hey! Heyhey!
（マコ）ヘイヘイヘイヘーイ
ヘイ ヘイヘイヘイ…
Heyheyheyhey! Hey!
...Heyheyhey! Hey! Heyhe—
Watch where you're driving, jackass!
（流子）バカ野郎！ 気を付けろ
（マコのせきこみ）
What's the matter?
Did you break down?
どうした？ 故障か
うわっ 蟇郡先輩が釣れた
I reeled in Gamagoori!
Gamagoori! You followed me
all the way out here?
が… 蟇郡
ここまで追ってきたのか？
Calm down.
慌てるな ここで貴様と
戦うつもりはない
I have no intention of fighting you here.
何？
Come again?
My fight with you will be at the
Sudden Death Runoff Election.
（蟇郡）
貴様とは決戦闘兵の場で戦う
What do you want, then?
じゃあ何の用だ
（蟇郡）乗れ
（流子）えっ
Get in.
I am Gamagoori Ira, Honnouji Academy Disciplinary Bureau Chairman.
（蟇郡）俺は本能字学園
風紀部委員長 蟇郡苛(いら)
If we come across a Honnouji Academy student in trouble off campus,
校外で困っている
本能字学園の生徒がいたら—
それを助けるのも
俺たち風紀委員の公務だ
it is the duty of us committee
members to assist them.
お前だろうと例外ではない 乗れ
That holds true even for you. Get in.
しかし…
...But we can't—
（マコ）ウヒョー
ふかふかだよ このシート
This seat is so soft!
新車だね ピカピカだね
It must be brand-new!
It's all sparkly!
And your license is
all sparkly and new, too!
しかも免許も
ピカピカの取りたてだよ
流子ちゃんドライブだよ
Ryuuko, let's go for a drive!
Get in, get in, let's go!
乗ろうよ 乗ろうよ
レッツゴーだよ
On a drive, on a drive!
On a drive to Hell!
（マコ）
♪ ドライブ ドライブ
Goin' totally upside-down
to the bottom of the pit! Hey!
We've left the track
and we're gonna crash!
Matoi, make her stop
that god-awful singing.
（蟇郡）纏(まとい)
その耳障りな歌をやめさせろ
Hit someone from behind and you get a pileup!
（流子）あたしが止めて
止まるマコだと思うのか？
Do you honestly think
anyone can make her stop?
We'll all go to Hell together!
True. Mankanshoku has
never seen a red light in her life.
On a drive, on a drive, on a drive to Hell!
（蟇郡）満艦飾(まんかんしょく)に
赤信号はなかったな
そうだよ 私の人生信号は
いつも黄色だよ
That's right!
My life's traffic lights are all yellow!
一生 注意か それも真理だ
"In life, proceed with caution", eh?
There is truth in that.
（ミュージック
ホーン音）
うっ 無礼な
ここは追い越し禁止だぞ
What nerve!
This is a no-passing zone!
道交法を知らんのか？
Doesn't he know the rules of the road?!
Mako, get down!
（流子）マコ 伏せろ
（マコ）わあ
えいっ
Who the hell are they?!
（流子）何だよ あいつら
（マコ）うわー
（蟇郡）ヤツらは—
The Automotive Club and Airsoft Club
merged to form the Automotive Airsoft Club.
自動車部とサバイバルゲーム部が
合併した サバイバル自動車部だ
I'm the one that they're gunning for.
今 狙われているのは俺だ
お前の神衣(かむい)が ほかの人間には
着られないことは—
We have Oogure Maiko to thank for proving that no one but you can wear your Godrobe.
大暮舞子(おおぐれまいこ)が証明したからな
（流子）チッ 欲しいのは
三つ星極制服ってわけか
So they're after your
Three-Star Ultima Uniform, huh?
（マコ）流子ちゃん あれ！
Ryuuko, look at that!
What's the matter, Gamagoori?
（轟(とどろき)）どうした 蟇郡！
Do you think you can escape Automotive Airsoft
Club President Todoroki Ryousuke in that clunker,
AUTOMOTIVE
AIRSOFT
CLUB
PRESIDENT
TODOROKI
RYOUSUKE
このサバイバル自動車部部長
轟輌輔(りょうすけ)から—
そんな車で逃げ切れると思うか
風紀部委員長様よう！
Mr. Disciplinary Bureau Chairman?!
（流子）
どうやら とんでもない車に
乗っちまったようだな
Looks like we picked the
wrong car to hitch a ride with.
Whoa!
Interesting!
（蟇郡）面白い
But can you keep up
with my driving skills?
だが俺のハンドルさばきに
ついてこられるかな
H-How can this be?!
（蟇郡）な… なんと！
（流子）“なんと”じゃねえ
Don't give me that!
If you spin the steering wheel like a maniac, you're obviously gonna spin out!
ハンドルむやみに回したら
こうなるに決まってるだろうが！
Is your brain as rookie as your license?
てめえの脳みそ若葉マークかー！
Ow... You okay, Mako?
（流子）あっ あたた
大丈夫か？ マコ
Oh, you guys think
you're hot stuff, huh?
おいおい てめえら
調子に乗りやがって
（蟇郡）纏 お前は手を出すな
（流子）何？
Matoi, stay out of this.
What?
（蟇郡）俺の過ちは俺が償う
It was my mistake, so I'll fix it.
We have you cornered, Gamagoori!
（轟）追い詰めたぞ 蟇郡
泣こうが わめこうが
容赦はしねえ
Cry and shout all you want,
but you'll get no mercy from us!
フン 貴様らごときに
涙を見せる俺ではない
It'll take more than the
likes of you to make me cry!
And even if I did shed a tear, I would wipe it away myself!
よしんば落涙(らくるい)したとて
俺の涙は俺が拭く
I would ask no one else to!
他人の手は借りん
ケッ これでも
大口がたたけるか！
Still talking big, huh?
Let him have it!
食らえ！
（マコ）キャッ うう
（部員たち）熱 熱っ…
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Shackle Regalia!
（蟇郡）三つ星極制服…
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA
H-He transformed!
（部員）か… 変わった
チッ ひるむんじゃねえ
やっちまえ
Don't let that faze you! Get him!
Man, that thing is hard.
（流子）なんて硬さだ
（蟇郡）ただ硬いだけではない
It's not just hard.
（蟇郡）
おお〜っ おぅ おお… いいぞ
That's it! More! Punish me more!
もっとだ もっと攻めろ
俺を攻めてみろ
I've been a bad boy!
貴様らが俺を攻めるたび
俺の心がムチ打たれるのだ
Punish me! Every time you
punish me, my heart is whipped!
Yes! The more it's whipped,
the stronger I become!
そうだ ムチ打たれて強くなる
あのときの俺のようにな
Just like I was that day!
RINNE-DOU JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL
FIVE
YEARS
AGO
Go on! Hurry up and jump!
（北条(ほうじょう)）さあ 早く飛び降りろよ
You got milk on my uniform.
（今川(いまがわ)）あなたが私の服に
牛乳かけたんでしょう
（男子生徒）それは はずみで…
That was an accident!
（北条）だから飛び降りたら
許してやるって言ってんだよ
That's why we're saying we'll
let it slide if you take the leap.
（蟇郡）貴様ら何をしている！
（学生たち）あ？
You there! What are you doing?!
GAMAGOORI
IRA
THIRD YEAR
JUNIOR HIGH
Well, well, if it isn't the
Student Council President.
（北条）おやおや
生徒会長さんのご登場だ
But we'd like you to stay out of this.
でも黙って見ていてもらおうか
（男子生徒）
蟇郡さん いいんです
俺が逆らうとオヤジがクビになる
Gamagoori, it's okay!
If I don't do as he says,
my dad will be fired!
Yeah, his dad works at
my old man's company.
（北条）
そう こいつのオヤジさんは
ウチの会社に勤めてるんだよ
（今川）そして私のパパは
この町の警察署長
And my daddy is
this town's chief of police.
He covers up little
things like this for me.
多少の事件はもみ消してくれる
（蟇郡）北条 今川
貴様らそれでも人間か！
Houjou! Imagawa! Do you two even call yourselves human beings?!
We are certainly human.
（北条）そうだよ 人間だよ
It's because we're human that we understand the fear of status and authority.
人間だから地位とか権力の怖さが
わかるんじゃないか
家族のために自分が犠牲になるのも
人間ならではよね
And sacrificing himself for the good of his family is the mark of a true human being, right?
Now, hurry up and jump!
さあ 早く落ちなさい！
Wait!
待て！
How about that, Gamagoori?
（北条）どうだ 蟇郡
（蟇郡）くっ
You can play at being
righteous all you want,
貴様がいくら正義漢面しようと
この輪廻堂(りんねどう)中学じゃー
but here at Rinne-dou Junior High,
no one can oppose us.
俺たちに逆らえる者なんか
いないんだよ
（蟇郡）クソー！
Damn it!
（男子生徒）ヒィー
（北条）ええ！
（皐月）フッ さすが
我が鬼龍院特製のトランポリン
The Kiryuuin Deluxe Trampoline
bounces well, doesn't it?
よく跳ねる
（男子生徒）ヒー
（蟇郡）来い
Come here!
離してください 俺が無事だと
オヤジがクビになるんです
Let go!
If I live, my dad's job is history!
You needn't worry about that.
（皐月）その心配は無用だ
I've already bought out
that despicable company.
その卑劣漢の会社は
私が買い取った
What the hell?
What are you, a new student?
何だお前 新入生か？
何 寝言ほざいてんだよ
What's this crap you're spouting?
そうよ くだらないこと言ってると
パパに逮捕させるわよ
Yeah! If you keep talking rubbish, I'll have my daddy arrest you!
Kiryuuin Products Absorbs Houjou Products In Merger
Chief Of Police Imagawa Accused Of Bribery
Mr. Imagawa Dumbfounded by Sudden Dismissal
お前の父親は
たった今 解任された
Your father has just been
relieved of his duties.
If you don't believe me, look at this.
信じられないなら これを見ろ
Kiryuuin Products Absorbs Houjou Products In Merger
Chief Of Police Imagawa Accused Of Bribery
Mr. Imagawa Dumbfounded by Sudden Dismissal
Wh-What the hell?!
な… 何だこりゃ
Who do you think you are?!
Guys! Make her suffer!
ふざけるな！
みんな 痛い目 見せてあげて
１年Ａ組 鬼龍院皐月
First Year Class A, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
FIRST
YEAR
JUNIOR
HIGH
As of this moment, I rule over
every student in this junior high school.
今から この中学の全ての生徒を
私が支配する
Crooks like you who can't see
beyond their own self-interest
貴様らのような私利私欲の奸物(かんぶつ)は
これからは 私が許さぬ
will no longer be tolerated.
But you're relying on your
parents' influence too, are you not?
しかし お前も親の力を
利用してるじゃないか
How are you any
different from these two?
こいつらと どこが違う
These petty thugs are merely
leeching off their parents' power.
この小人(しょうじん)どもは ただ親の力に
すがっているだけだ
I am different!
私は違う 親の力 他の力
全てを利用する
I will exploit everything I can, be it
the power of my parents or others!
But I am the one who wields that power!
だが使うのは私だ
全ての力を飲み込んで
私自身の力とする
I absorb it all and make it my own!
It is a difference of resolve.
それが覚悟の違いだ
Resolve?
覚悟だと？
（皐月）蟇郡 覚悟なき者は
自分の涙も自分で拭えはしない
Gamagoori.
Those who lack resolve are incapable of even wiping away their own tears.
That was how I first met Lady Satsuki!
それが皐月様との出会いだった
And for two years, I waited.
そして俺は２年待った
I awaited her graduation,
enrolled in Honnouji Academy at her side,
皐月様の卒業を待ち
共に本能字学園に入学し—
and acquired this Ultima Uniform.
この極制服を手に入れたのだ
（流子）えっ じゃあ
おめえ いくつだよ
Hang on, how old are you?!
（蟇郡）俺は今年で二十歳だ
（マコ）どおりで老け顔だ
I turn twenty this year.
That explains your old-man face!
How much longer are
you gonna keep yapping?!
（轟）いつまで
おしゃべりしてんだよー
Yes! That's more like it!
（蟇郡）いいぞ〜 そうだ もっとだ
The more I'm punished, the more my
hardness towers mighty and strong!
攻められれば攻められるほど
俺の硬さは増し屹立(きつりつ)する
老け顔の変態だ
...He's a pervert with an old-man face...
Not pervert. Convert!
（蟇郡）変態ではない 変身だ
The instant I reach my climax,
頂点に達したとき満ち満ちに
満ちた俺の力を一気に—
the power that has been building up
...inside of me will burst out...
all at once!
解き放つ！
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Scourge Regalia!
THREE-STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SCOURGE
REGALIA
...Holy crap...
すっげえ
（鮮血）うっ 二段変身とはな
A secondary transformation, eh?
Back-Alley
Gas Station
Self-Serve
a steal !!
Back-Alley
Gas Station
Self-Serve
a steal !!
Back-Alley
Gas Station
Self-Serve
a steal !!
Back-Alley
Gas Station
Self-Serve
a steal !!
Be careful.
（蟇郡）気を付けて帰宅しろ
家に着くまでが遠足だ
They say "the picnic's not over until you reach home safely".
（流子）遠足じゃねえし
Jeez, it's not a picnic.
I'll be waiting for you at the
Sudden Death Runoff Election.
決戦闘兵で待っているぞ
俺たちの戦いに
ふさわしい場を用意する
I'll arrange a fitting spot for our battle.
何だと
Come again?
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
8:30AM
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
SEVEN
DAYS
LATER
時間です 皐月様
It is time, Lady Satsuki.
Fellow comrades of Honnouji Academy!
本能字学園の同胞よ
You have done well to struggle through seven days of mortal combat
７日間の死戦をくぐ抜けて—
to gather here to take part in the Sudden Death Runoff Election!
よく決戦闘兵の
この場に集まってくれた
However, your battle
has only just begun!
だが 諸君らの戦いは
これからだ
Each and every battle over the
last seven days has been recorded!
これまでの７日間の戦いは
全て記録されている
それを踏まえ
ここでの戦いの成果により—
With that in mind,
I will begin by designating new Three-Star students based on the results of the battle here!
まず新しい三つ星の生徒から
決めさせてもらう
何だ
What the—?
There are five towers
in the schoolyard!
（皐月）学園に立つ５つの塔
Those standing atop them will be considered front-running
candidates, and the election will be conducted!
ここに立つ者を上位候補として
決戦闘兵を行う
There she goes, being devious again!
こいつ…
また こんなやり方を…
ペッ 上等だ！
Fine by me!
Well, well. I see you're not just
called the Four Devas for show.
なるほどな 四天王の名前は
ダテじゃないか
Did you expect anything else?
当然の結果でしょ
（蟇郡）皐月様！
Lady Satsuki!
We, the Four Devas, hereby propose a
new rule for the Sudden Death Runoff Election!
我ら四天王 この決戦闘兵の場で
新たなルールを提案する
We each wish to be allowed to face Matoi Ryuuko in single combat.
１対１で纏流子との戦いを
所望したい
If we're going to fight her anyway,
this grand stage is just the place for it.
（蛇崩）どうせ戦うなら
このくらい派手な舞台じゃないとね
I believe it would be a fitting way to
cap off the climax of the Naturals Election.
（犬牟田）壊惨総戦挙の
クライマックスを飾るには—
ふさわしいかと思いますが
フッ それも一興か
This should prove
just as amusing, huh?
NATURALS
ELECTION
POLLING PLACE
This is a king of the hill final battle!
KING OF
THE HILL
FINAL
BATTLE
Matoi! Battle the Four Devas
and emerge victorious!
纏 四天王と戦い 勝ち抜け
そうすれば お前の
父親の死について語ってやろう
Do so, and I shall tell you the
truth behind your father's death.
Say what?!
何だと
Matoi! This is where
I will face you in battle!
（蟇郡）纏 これが
お前との戦いの場だ
タアー
俺は皐月様の絶対の盾
I am Lady Satsuki's
impenetrable shield!
貴様ごとき ここで打ち砕く！
And this is where I am going to crush you!
I accept!
受けて立つぜ！
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
（流子）人衣(じんい)一体 神衣鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Before the bell rings
chime ga naru mae ni
I sneak out of school
kugurinuketa
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
The pointless conversations
tawai no nai kaiwa
Keep going on and on
togirenu mama
As I walk down the slope
sakamichi wo kudatteku
I have nothing to do
nani wo suru demo naku
And nowhere to go
yuku ate sae mo naku
Right now, all I do
tada atashi ima wa ne
Is ignore any and all warnings
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Because I still want to be free
mada mada suki ni sasete
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
To be an exemplary student
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
And take the back alley
rojiura no nukemichi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
amai yuuwaku wa michi
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
A king of the hill final battle!
（鮮血）塔首(とうしゅ)頂上決戦
最初の相手は蟇郡苛
Her first opponent is Gamagoori Ira!
GAMAGOORI IRA
From Shackle Regalia to Scourge Regalia,
縛(しばり)の装から死縛(しばき)の装
驚異の二段変態に見よ
feast your eyes on his fearsome, two-stage transformation!
TRANSFORMATION
ガチガチの堅物が
戦場に屹立(きつりつ)する
HARDASS
This straight-laced hardass stands
mighty and erect on the battlefield!
STANDS
次回 キルラキル
「チャンスは一度」
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"A Once in a Lifetime Chance"!
EPISODE 9
A ONCE IN A
LIFETIME CHANCE